Oh, come on!
It's your Thanksgiving too. Instead of
watching football, you could help.
추수감사절인데 풋볼만
보고 있지 말고 좀 도와줘
We know.
- 그래
- 알았어
레이첼, 동그란 원 안에
마시멜로 좀 넣을래?
You wanna put the marshmallows
in concentric circles.
No, you want to put them
아니, 동그란 원 안에
마시멜로 넣는 건 네가 해
I want to do this.
난 이거나 할래
Every year.
매번 이렇다니까
The One With the Football
To the 10, to the 5.
Touchdown, Giants!
You know, for once, I am gonna try
to watch one of these things.
나도 잠깐 엉덩이 붙이고 앉아서
풋볼이나 봐야겠다
Halftime.
전반 끝났다
Who wants to throw the ball around?
Get a little 3-on-3 going?
우리, 시합 안 할래?
편 갈라서 한 판 하자
재밌겠다
-That would be fun!
-Can I play too?
나도 해도 돼?
풋볼 한번도 안해 봤는데
I've never played football, ever.
Great! You can cover Chandler.
그럼, 챈들러 커버해
I don't really want to play.
아니, 난 하기 싫어
You never do anything
since you and Janice broke up.
하자, 너 재니스랑 헤어지고
아무 의욕도 없잖아
Not true.
그런 소리 마
욕실 가운 입고, 종일
땅콩 버터 먹고 싶고
I wanted to wear my bathrobe
and eat peanut clusters all day.
And start drinking in the morning.
Don't say I don't have goals!
아침부터 술독에 빠지고 싶어
나도 목표가 있는 놈이야
You have to start getting
over her, all right?
챈들러, 이제 그만 잊어버려
If you play, maybe it'll
take your mind off Janice.
시합하면서 시원한 바람을 쐬면
재니스도 잊혀질 거야
If you don't, everyone will be mad at
you because the teams won't be even.
너 시합 안 하면 숫자가
안 맞으니까 다들 화낼 거야
- 하자
- 알았어, 할게
All right, I'll play.
야호!
Let's do it! Ross?
- 하자, 로스
- 뭐?
-What?
-Wanna play football?
풋볼하자
Monica and I aren't supposed
to play football.
모니카랑 난 풋볼하면 안돼
Says who? Your mom?
누가 그래, 너희 엄마?
그래
Every Thanksgiving, we used
to have a touch football game...
추수감사절 때마다 우린
풋볼 시합을 했어
...called The Geller Bowl.
일명 '겔러볼'이라고 했지
설마, 그게 자랑은 아니겠지?
No, no, no. You say that proudly!
로스 오빠랑 난 주장이었어
Anyway, Ross and l
were always captains.
It got kind of competitive,
and one year, Geller Bowl Vl...
서로 이기려고 눈이 멀었는데
어느 해인가...
내가 실수로 오빠 코를
부러뜨렸어
... I accidentally broke Ross' nose.
그건 실수가 아니었어
It was so not an accident.
She saw I was about to tag her,
so she threw...
내가 따라붙으니까 피둥피둥한
팔로 내 얼굴을 갈기고
... her big fat grandma-arm
elbow in my face...
냅다 도망쳤어
...and just kept running.
어쨌든 우리가 터치다운했어
To score the winning touchdown,
by the way.
시합에 이기지도 못했잖아
You did not win the game.
The touchdown didn't count...
... because of the spectacularly
illegal, and savage, nose-breaking.
터치다운은 기록되지도 않았어
불법 행위에 야만 행위였거든
코를 부러뜨린 거 말야
I won the game.
내가 이겼어
Yeah? Then how come you
didn't get the Geller Cup?
그럼 왜 '겔러컵'을 못 받았지?
There was a Geller Cup?
'겔러컵'도 있었어?
그래, 시합에서 이기면 받는
트로피였어
Yes, the trophy you got
if you won the game.
아빠가 무승부라고 하셨지
우리 싸우는 거에 신물이 나셨거든
But Dad said nobody won,
and he was sick of our fighting.
그래서 트로피를 가져가서...
So he took the trophy...
...threw it in the lake.
호수에 던져버리셨어
And was the curse lifted?
그래서 저주가 시작된 거야?
Anyway...
어쨌든...
... Mom said we weren't
allowed to play football again.
엄마가 그때부터 다시는
풋볼 못하게 하셨어
You know what?
I think we should play a game.
괜찮아
이제 시합해도 될 거야
I mean, come on.
It's been 12 years.
벌써 12년이나 지났잖아
Can I see you for a second?
잠깐 좀 볼까?
뭐?
Wuss!
All right, we're gonna play.
좋아, 하자
Wait. How we gonna get there?
My mom won't let me cross the street.
잠깐, 공원에 어떻게 가지?
엄마가 길 건너지 말랬는데
Here you go.
피비, 받아
좋아, 시작하자
-Let's bring it in.
-Wait.
나한테 던져, 나한테!
Honey, throw it to me!
Here you go.
간다
That almost hit me in the face!
얼굴 맞을 뻔했어
We have to pick captains.
좋아, 우리 주장 고르자
And then "Tenilles."
꼬붕들도
So how do we decide that?
어떻게 하는 건데?
- 찍기 하자
- 뭐?
-Why don't we just bunny up?
-What?
-Bunny!
- 찍자구
- 찍는 거야
로스 오빠랑 내가 주장이야
Looks like Ross and I are captains.
I bunnied first,
so I get to pick first. Joey.
- 나부터 찍을게, 먼저 고를 거야
- 좋아
- 조이
- 고마워
-Thank you.
-Monica!
모니카, 난 네 친구야
I'm your best friend.
Sweetie, don't worry,
you'll get picked.
자기도 뽑힐 테니까 기다려봐
챈들러
- 로스?
- 피비
봐, 자기 고르잖아
Sweetie, now I pick you.
고른 게 아니라
나만 남은 거잖아
You don't pick me.
You're stuck with me!
좋아, 그럼 쓰레기통에서
가로등까지 하는 거다
Okay. So let's see.
Let's play from the trash can
to the light post, right?
Two-hand touch. We'll kick off.
우리가 시작할게
People, listen.
I've got 28 minutes...
좋아, 잘 들어
정확히 28분 후에
... before I have to baste again.
부저가 울리는 거다
Wow, just like in the pros.
꼭 프로 같은데
Okay, huddle up!
-Huddle up over here!
-Wait for me! Wait for me!
좋아, 작전 타임
이리 와
잠깐, 기다려
Oh, cool! My first huddle.
신난다
작전 타임은 처음이야
- 좋아
- 챈들러를 어떻게 생각하니?
So what do you guys really think
of Chandler?
- 피비, 뭐하는 건지 알아?
- 그럼
You know what you're doing, right?
조이가 공을 잡으면 너랑 내가
블로킹하는 거야
Joey will catch it.
We'll block.
블로킹이 뭐야?
What's "block"?
-I thought you knew what you were doing.
-I thought you meant in life!
뭐하는지 안다고 했잖아
시합 얘긴 줄 몰랐지
해산
Break!
The ball is Janice.
이 공은 재니스다
Son of a!
이 나쁜... 조심해
-Come on!
-I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
미안, 미안해
그냥 손으로 던진다
You know what?
We're just gonna throw it.
I got it!
- 내가 받을게
- 뛰어!
Go, go, go!
Score! Seven to nothing!
7대 빵입니다!
Honey, you okay?
괜찮아?
Come on, let's go.
그래, 가자
Losers walk.
패자가 걸어가네
Yeah? Losers talk.
패자가 말을 하네
그만해, 패자가 까부네
Actually, losers rhyme.
Forty-three...
43, 74...
...seventy-four....
You wanna go shotgun?
- 그냥 할래?
- 그래
- 간다!
- 원 미시시피, 투 미시시피, 쓰리!
-One Mississippi, two Mississippi....
-Over here! Over here!
여기야, 여기
I almost caught it!
받을 뻔했어
- 7대 7 될 뻔했어
- 그래
Great. Now the score's
seven to almost seven.
On this play, I want you to do
a down-and-out to the right, okay?
이번엔 쭉 내려가서
오른쪽으로 가는 거다
- 알았어
- 해산!
-Break!
-Wait. What am I gonna do?
잠깐, 난 어떡해?
넌... 그냥 돌아
You?
You go long.
얼마 동안?
How long?
Until we start to look very small.
눈앞이 노래질 때까지
- 알았어
- 해산
Break!
준비, 간다!
One Mississippi
원 미시시피, 투 미시시피
받아, 받아!
Switch! Switch! Switch!
안돼, 안돼!
Thanks for stopping our ball.
공 잡아줘서 고마워요
You are playing American football?
- 미식 축구하는 거예요?
- 네
Wow! You're, like,
from a whole other country!
외국에서 오셨나봐요
I'm Dutch.
네덜란드예요
안녕, 난 조이예요
Hi, I'm Joey.
I am Margha.
난 마하예요
Sorry, Dutch, I didn't get
that last little bit.
미안해요, 네덜란드
뒷말은 못 알아듣겠어요
조이, 풋볼하다 말고 뭐해?
안녕, 난 챈들러예요
You wanna play football or
Hi, I'm Chandler.
Hello, Chandler.
안녕, 챈들러
이름이 네덜란드인데
마한이라고도 한대
Her name is Dutch and also "Margham."
- 마하예요
- 마카
- 마하
- 마하아안
뭐해? 계속해야지
두 번째 다운이야
Come on, guys! Let's go!
Second down!
-Hello? It's third down.
-No, it's not. It's second.
세 번째야
웃기지 마, 두 번째야
Wow.
- 와우
- 뭐가 와우야?
"Wow" what?
How it just amazes me that you're
still pulling stuff like this.
잘났다고 박박 우기는 거
보니까 놀랍기만 하다
우겼다고?
두 번째 맞잖아
-Pulling what? It's second down.
-Okay, it's second down.
그래, 두 번째라고 해
불쌍해서 봐준다
Take all the second downs you need.
-I heard that.
-Well, I said it loud.
다 들었어
들으라고 한 소리야
It is okay if I stay and watch?
여기서 구경해도 돼요?
-Just sit right there.
-Yeah, why don't you stick around?
- 그럼요, 앉아서 봐요
- 어서 앉아요
-That went well.
-I think so.
- 잘됐다
- 그럼
I was thinking about asking her
for her number.
전화번호 물어보면 어떨까?
고맙지만 내가 직접 해야
점수가 올라갈 거야
Thanks, man, but it makes a stronger
statement if I ask for it myself.
I was thinking about for me, as part
of that getting-over-Janice thing.
그게 아니라
날 위해서 물어봐 달라고...
재니스를 잊으라고 했잖아
Oh, yeah. That.
그야 그렇지
If it means that much,
I'll let you have her.
- 네 생각이 그렇다면 양보할게
- 고마워
Thanks.
뭐? 양보한다고?
"Let me have her"?
You mean if you didn't,
I wouldn't have a shot?
나 혼자 나서봤자
어림없다는 소리야 뭐야?
I don't like to say it out loud...
큰 소리 내고 싶진 않지만
... but yeah!
그래!
괜찮아, 넌 여자엔 약하지만
숫자에는 강하잖아
We all have our strengths.
You're better with numbers and stuff.
숫자?
숫자로 밀어부치려고?
Math? You're giving me math?
좋아, 관두자
All right, you know what?
Forget about it.
You go for the girl.
We'll see who gets her.
양보하지 마
누가 이기나 붙어보자구
I want you to run a post-pattern
to the left. And, sweetie
챈들러, 왼쪽으로 무작정
달리는 거야, 알았지?
- 그리고 자기?
- 알아, 계속 돌라고?
Yeah, I know. Go long.
All I'm doing is running
back and forth from the huddle.
난 작전 타임이나 하고
왔다갔다만 하는 것 같아
Well, you wanna just stay out there?
그럼 나가서 구경할래?
- 잠깐 좀 볼까?
- 그래
Can I see that for a second?
좋아
Okay, let's go.
- 좋아, 간다
- 간다!
-I got Chandler!
-Hike!
원 미시시피, 투 미시시피,
쓰리 미시시피
One Mississippi, two Mississippi,
three Mississippi.
놓쳤잖아
Fumble!
What's the matter with you?
This is my favorite jersey.
뭐하는 거야?
내가 제일 좋아하는 옷인데
두 개로 갈라줬잖아
Well, now you have two.
Hey, I am good at math!
나 계산 잘하지?
That's it. I was still
gonna let you have her.
좋아, 양보하려고 했는데
But now, prepare to feel
bad about yourself.
없었던 걸로 하고
자존심 상할 각오나 하셔
그래, 평생 각오하면서
살고 있다
I've been preparing for that
my entire life!
Or something about you that's mean!
지금 네 얘길 하는 거야!
Come on, guys. Let's go.
좋아, 간다
Tie score.
We're running out of time.
동점이야, 시간 없어
Forty-two, 38, hike!
42, 38, 간다!
내가 받을게
I got it!
Broken boobs!
팔 부러졌나봐
- 피비, 달려
- 피비, 뛰어
-Pheebs, run!
-Run, Phoebe, run!
- 터치다운이야
- 터치다운!
Touchdown! Touchdown!
아니, 부저가 울렸어
이건 점수에 포함 안 돼
The buzzer buzzed.
It doesn't count.
-After the snap.
-Before the snap.
- 부저는 나중에 울렸어
- 전에 울렸어
- 나중에
- 전에
-After.
-Before.
-Does it really matter?
-Yes!
- 그게 문제가 돼?
- 그럼!
But I made a touchdown.
It was my first touchdown.
터치다운했어, 최초의
터치다운이야, 그러니까...
피비, 그건 알지만
점수는 안돼
Pheebs, that's great.
Doesn't count.
-Does so count.
-Cheater, cheater, compulsive eater.
- 왜 안된다는 거야?
- 사기꾼이 우기기까지 하네
세상에
Oh, my God!
That's fine. Maybe you haven't
grown up, but I have.
좋아, 오빠는 유치하게 굴어
난 오빠랑 달라
그래
다리나 부러져라
Dead leg!
좋아, 속임수를 써서 이기겠다?
맘대로 해
Okay, fine. You want to win
by cheating, go ahead.
The touchdown does count.
You win.
피비, 터치다운했다고 쳐
네가 이겼어
- 신난다!
- 아니
또 오빠 술수에
넘어갈 줄 알아?
I won't do this again. I wanna
beat you when you can't blame it...
코뼈가 부러졌다고, 귀가 짝짝이라
부저가 빨랐다고 핑계 대지마
...on the broken nose or the buzzer
or the fact that you might have mono.
Let's just call this tie score
and it's halftime.
동점이라고 하고
후반에 다시 하자구
난 사기꾼하고
시합 안 해
First, I don't play with cheaters.
Second of all,
you know I had swollen glands!
하고 싶어도
다리 부러져서 못해!
You know what? I think you'll play.
시합 안하곤 못 배길걸
왜 못 배겨?
Oh, really? Why's that?
이기면 이걸 가져가니까
Because the winner gets this.
The Geller Cup!
'겔러컵'이잖아
사자 머리 인형
너희도 봤니?
Is everybody else seeing a
troll doll nailed to a two-by-four?
응
Okay, good.
그렇군
Where the hell did you get that?
어디서 났어?
When you went to the hospital
for your nose...
엄마 아빠가 오빠
병원에 데려갔을 때
...I swam into the lake
and fished it out.
내가 호수에 헤엄쳐
들어가 꺼냈지
That cup is mine!
내 컵이야
No, it's not. You want it,
you're gonna have to win it.
아니, 갖고 싶으면
시합에서 이기면 되잖아
So are we not
having dinner at all?
좋아, 근데 저녁은 언제 먹어?
Come on, let's go.
It's time to get serious. Huddle up.
피비, 이리 와
시합해야지, 작전 타임
IKeep your head in the game.
조이, 시합에 집중해
It's hard, you know?
His huddle's close to the Dutch girl.
그게 말처럼 쉬워?
챈들러가 여자 가까이 있잖아
좋아, 챈들러만 해결하면
시합에 집중할 수 있겠어?
If I take Chandler out of the running,
will you be able to focus?
-What are you gonna do?
-Just make sure he catches the ball.
어떻게 하려고?
공이나 받게 해
I'll do the rest.
- 나머지는 내가 할게
- 알았어
-Come on, you wuss!
-Okay, come on.
- 가자
- 좋아
I got it!
Come on! This way!
Come on!
조심해!
Look out!
Tackled by a girl!
Bet you don't see that every day.
여자한테 태클 당했대요
이런 구경하기 힘들답니다
왜 태클을 걸고 난리야?
What's with the tackling?
What?
왜? 건드리기만 했는데
넘어진 거야
I just touched him and he went over.
Okay. You wanna play rough?
We can play rough.
거칠게 하겠다 이거지?
좋았어
Let's get ready to rumble!
-Go, go, go!
-Get her! Get her!
I love this game!
너무 재밌다
Where'd you get that?
어디서 난 거야?
I went really long.
한참 놀았더니 배고파서...
Forty-two to 21.
42대 21
상대가 안돼, 우리가 이겼지롱
Like the turkey, Ross is done!
네가 이긴 것도 당연하지
너부터 팀을 골랐으니까
You got to pick
first, so you got the better team.
우기지 마
Pathetic! Why can't you
just accept that we're winning...
그냥 받아들이면 되잖아
내가 오빠보다 낫다는 증거야
... because I'm better than you?
Oh, what a great argument.
Exhaling!
할 말 없으니까 코웃음으로
무마하시겠다?
All right, I'll prove it to you.
좋아, 내가 증명해 보일까?
조이랑 레이첼을 바꿔도
우리 팀이 이길 수 있어
I'll trade you Joey for Rachel
and I'll still win the game.
What? The guys against the girls?
뭐? 남자 대 여자라구?
That's ridiculous because
I'm only down by three touchdowns.
말도 안되는 소리하지 마
내가 터치다운 세 번은 한다
Then bring it on!
그럼 해봐
Unless you're afraid you might lose
to a bunch of girls.
여자들한테 질까봐
무서워서 못하는 거 아냐?
Fine. Rachel, you're with Monica.
Joey, you're with me.
좋아, 레이첼, 모니카 편 해
조이, 넌 우리 편이야
I can't believe you're trading me.
날 바꾸는 거야?
Let's see what it's like
to be on a winning team for a change.
이리 와, 레이첼
이기는 팀에 들어오면 좋잖아
나 게임해도 돼?
You're gonna let me play?
All right, then!
좋아!
게임 끝났어요?
식사하는 거예요?
The game is over? We eat now?
아뇨, 아직이요
팀을 바꾸는 거예요
The game's not over.
We're switching teams.
Chandler finds me so intimidating that
it's better if we're on the same team.
같은 팀에서 뛰면 챈들러가
나 때문에 실력발휘 못할걸요
Okay, let's play.
Let's go.
좋아, 그럼 시작하자
Hold on a second.
잠깐만, 조이
Where do Dutch people come from?
네덜란드 사람들이
어디서 왔게?
펜실배니아 네덜란드는
펜실배니아에서 왔지
Well, the Pennsylvania Dutch
come from Pennsylvania.
And the other Dutch people?
다른 사람은?
네덜란드 근처에서 왔을까?
They come from somewhere near
the Netherlands, right?
웃겼어
Nice try.
The Netherlands is this
make-believe place...
네덜란드는 피터팬이랑
팅커벨이 사는 동화 속 나라야
...where Peter Pan
and Tinker Bell live.
맙소사
Oh, my.
Enough "geography for the insane."
Let's play ball.
지리 공부는 나중에 하고
시합이나 하자구
- 아니, 나 얘하고 시합 못해
- 나도 마찬가지야
I'm not playing with this guy.
-Fine with me.
-I've had enough of this.
좋아, 더는 못 봐줘
솔직히 말해봐요
Let's just cut to the chase.
Heidi, which of my boys do you like?
둘 중에 누가 더 좋아요?
지금 뭐하는 거야?
What are you doing?
Which do I like?
둘 중에요?
데이트하자고 한다면요
풍차 나라에 누굴 데려갈래요?
Yeah, for dating, general merriment,
taking back to your windmill?
Well, if I had to choose right now...
지금 그걸 골라야 한다면
좀 이상하긴 하지만...
...which, by the way,
I find really weird...
... I would have to say Chandler.
- 챈들러로 하죠
- 좋았어!
잠깐, 질문을 이해 못한 거
같은데
Wait a minute.
She didn't understand the question.
그럼 후크 선장이 직접
설명해주시지
Why don't you have Captain Hook
explain it to her?
미안해요, 조이
제 진심이에요
I'm sorry. That is my truth.
You hear that? That is her truth,
Mr. "I'll Let You Have Her"!
들었지? 진심이라잖아
양보맨 씨!
I win! You suck! I rule all!
내가 이기고 네가 졌어
다같이 축하의 박수를!
Mini-wave in celebration of me!
우후!
I am now thinking I would like
to change my answer to "no one."
다시 생각해보니까
아무도 안 고르는 게 좋겠어요
What?
뭐라구요?
I now find you shallow...
이제 보니까 당신 너무 얄팍하고
가벼워요, 안녕
...and a dork.
Bye-bye.
Nice going.
안됐다, 앞으로도 여자랑
잠자리 할 일은 없겠구나
You just saved yourself
a couple months of sex.
It doesn't matter,
because she picked me.
그게 중요한 게 아냐
중요한 건 날 골랐단 거지
From now on,
I get the dates...
이제부터 난 데이트할 때
넌 "준비, 땡"이나 하면서 놀라구
...and you stay home on Saturday
nights watching Ready, Set, Cook!
Save the breakthroughs for therapy.
The clock is ticking.
싸움은 나중에 하자
이럴 시간이 없어
We have no time and we are
losing to girls.
우리가 지고 있어
여자들한테 지고 있다구
We're not gonna lose to girls.
여자들한테 왜 져?
42대 21이야
It's 42-21!
This sucks!
I was just up by that much!
말도 안돼
아까 내가 다 이겨 놨는데
Are we playing football or what?
Come on, you hairy-backed Marys!
시합하는 거야 마는 거야?
털복숭이 친구들!
We have to do this.
We're playing for women everywhere.
꼭 이겨야 돼
세상 모든 여자들을 위해서야
지금까지 만났던 재수없는
데이트 상대들을 생각해봐
Think about every lousy date
you ever had.
사랑을 나누면서도 한쪽 눈으론
TV 보느라 정신없는 남자들을!
Every guy who kept one eye
on the TV while you were making out.
Oh, my God. You dated someone
with a glass eye too?
너도 한쪽 안경 쓴 사람이랑
데이트해봤어?
Come on, okay? This is for
all womankind. Let's kill them!
세상 모든 여자들을 위한
시합이야
- 쓸어버리자구
- 그래, 쓸어버리자!
Yeah! IKill them!
All right,
I want to kill them too.
좋아, 솔직히 나도 쓸어버리고
싶지만 쟤들은 남자야
But they're boys.
어떻게 남자 셋을 이겨?
You know, how are we gonna
beat three boys?
A minute and a half left
and we're down by two points.
아직 1분 30초 남았으니까
2점은 딸 수 있어
2점이면 돼
Two points, ladies.
Phoebe, you do a buttonhook again.
피비, 후크 다시 풀어
Rachel, you go long.
레이첼, 넌 계속 돌아
싫어, 나도 시켜줘
아무도 날 커버 안한단 말야
No, don't make me go long.
Use me. They never cover me.
Honey, there's a reason.
그럴 만한 이유가 있어
I'm not lame, okay?
I can do something.
무시하지 마
나도 뭐든 할 수 있어
Would you let me throw?
This is my game too.
공 던질게, 던지게 해줘
나도 선수잖아
Let her throw the ball.
그래, 던지게 해줘
Sweep behind, I'll pitch it.
You throw it downfield to Phoebe.
좋아, 뒤에서 어슬렁거리다
공 받아서 피비한테 던져
- 그래
- 좋아
Thank you.
-Break!
해산, 해산
All right, here we go.
좋아, 32, 71, 간다!
Thirty-two, 71, hike!
One Mississippi, two Mississippi,
three Mississippi!
Go, go, go!
Catch it!
-I'm so sorry. Are you okay?
-No, I'm not okay!
미안, 괜찮아?
안 괜찮아!
They were coming at me
and I didn't know what to do.
미안해, 한꺼번에 달려드니까
어떻게 할지 모르겠더라구
Thirty seconds left on the timer.
30초 남았다
좋아, 그럼 사자 머리 인형
우리 거야?
So we get to take that
stupid troll thing home.
빨리, 시간 없단 말야
Come on! Hurry!
We're running out of time.
- 작전 타임!
- 좋아
Huddle up!
이번이 마지막이네
This is our last huddle!
All right, Phoebe, get open.
Rachel...
피비, 공 받을 준비하고
레이첼, 넌 계속 돌아
...go long.
Okay.
알았어
Break!
해산
I did it! Touchdown!
We did it!
내가 해냈다, 터치다운!
우리가 이겼어
야호!
You know? Funny thing, actually.
The end zone starts at that pole.
레이첼, 안됐지만...
엔드 존은 저 기둥부터야
5피트 모자라, 그러니까...
So you're five feet short.
So...
...we win!
우리가 이긴 거야
Yes, yes, yes!
잠깐, 어떻게 되는 거야?
Wait, explain something, though.
If nobody tagged Rachel,
then isn't the play still going?
아직 아웃 된 거 아니니까
시합 안 끝났잖아
- 이거 놔, 놓으란 말야
- 안돼, 네가 놔
-Let me in, let me in!
-No way! Let go!
- 이리 내놔!
- 난 연약한 여자라구
Let go?! I'm a tiny little woman!
그만하자, 추수감사절인데
이기고 지는 게 무슨 상관이야
Come on, it's Thanksgiving!
It's not important who wins or loses.
The important thing
is the Dutch girl picked me!
중요한 건 네덜란드 아가씨가
날 골랐다는 거야
Me, not you! Holland loves Chandler!
Thank you, Amsterdam! Good night!
네덜란드는 챈들러를 사랑해!
감사합니다, 아름다운 밤이에요!
We should play football
more often.
우리 풋볼 자주 하자
리그 같은 것도 있잖아
Maybe there's a league
we could join.
Isn't there a
"national football league"?
내셔널 풋볼 리그가
있지 않던가?
Yes, there is. They play on
Sundays and Monday nights.
그래, 있지
일요일, 월요일 밤에 시합해
아쉽다
월요일 밤에 일 나가는데
Oh, shoot! I work Monday nights.
This stuffing is amazing. Do you
think we should bring them some?
정말 맛있다
애들 불러와야 되지 않아?
When they're hungry,
they'll come in.
배고프면 들어오겠지
놔
-Let go!
-No, you let go!
- 네가 놔
- 싫어
왜 항상 우리만 공 붙들고
나동그러져 있지?
How come it's always us
left holding the ball?
I don't know. I guess the other
people just don't care enough.
몰라, 다른 사람들은
관심이 없나봐
Hey, it's starting to snow.
눈 온다
-Give it to me! Let go!
-Let it go! Come on, let go!
- 이거 놔
- 제발 좀 놔